

info@resumekraft.com

202-555-0120

Chicago, Illinois, US 💡

linkedin.com/resumekraft in

## PERSONAL AND FAMILY HISTORY

I am an educator with more than 25 years of experience. I have 14 years of experience in administration. I am married to Steve Dawson; married 10 years. I am the widow of Don Shotzman; married 29 years. I have two adult children, Matt and Lindsay Beth and three grandchildren. My father was a Southern Baptist pastor and my mother worked in the schools. My parents always taught us about servant leadership and education was highly valued. As a child I was taught to always "Do the right thing", a lesson that has always served me well.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Elementary Principal PreK-6

Fort Smith Public Schools Jun 2012 - Present

Elementary Principal 3-6

Mena Public Schools Jun 2009 - May 2011

Intermediate/ Middle School Principal 5-9

Dover Public Schools Jun 2007 - May 2009

Praxis Reviewer/ Assessor

Arkansas Dept. of Ed 2002 - 2011

Elementary Teacher- Grades 2 &4

Fort Smith Public Schools Aug 2001 - May 2007

Adjunct Instructor-ELA

Westark Community College 1995 - 1997

Elementary Lead Teacher-1,2,4

Harvest Time Christian School 1987 - 2001

## **EDUCATION**

Educational Leadership Ed.S

San Jose State University 2016 - 2018

Educational Administration, M.Ed

Northeastern University 1992 - 1994

Elementary Education B.S.E.

Arizona State University 1985 - 1987

**Elementary Education** 

University of South Florida 1981 - 1983

## **PROJECTS**

State Guiding Coalition

Member Present

Third Grade State Level Team

Administrator Lead Present